vitsoe.com 2013-08-22

# Vitsœ | Privacy policy

Vitsœ

  * Home
  * Shelves
  * Chairs
  * About
  * News
  * Contact
  * My Vitsœ

**The information we collect and how we use it**

When you register with us we need to know your name, postal address and email address.

We gather this information to allow us to communicate with you about our products and promotions.

In order to purchase on the website, we need to know your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and, if you are paying by card, your debit or credit card number and expiry date.

We gather this information to allow us to process your order and provide you with the best possible service.

The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to authenticate your identity, to validate your debit or credit card, to authorise the transaction and to communicate with you on any matter relating to the provision of the service in general. You specifically authorise us to transmit information to or to obtain information about you from third parties for these purposes.

We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an email message to email@vitsoe.com with “unsubscribe” in the subject field.

**Our use of “cookies”**

If you elect to complete a registration form on our site, we will place a cookie (a text file containing your preferences) in your computer’s browser so that you do not have to fill out the form again during your visit.

However, if you have switched cookies off in your browser, you may have to complete our registration form each time you download.

If you have cookies switched on, but you would prefer us not to place a cookie on your computer, we suggest that you do not complete our registration form; in which case we will email or post information to you.

**How we protect your information**

Information you provide to us remains confidential. The internal procedures of Vitsœ cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information and we will fully comply with all applicable UK data protection laws.

**Your details and how to update them**

You have the right at any time to request a copy of the personal data we hold on you.

If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example, if you change your email address or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by contacting us by fax, telephone or email.

**Your consent**

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this section of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Your continued use of the website constitutes your agreement to any such changes.

**How to contact us**

We welcome your views about our website and our Privacy Policy. Should you wish to contact us regarding our website or Privacy Policy please do so.

Vitsœ Limited is a company registered in England and Wales. Registered Office Centric Close, London NW1 7EP Company Number 2014122 VAT number GB 437 2545 47
